



Francisco Javier Sánchez Fernández

Nationality: Spanish Date of birth: 06/04/1999

\ Phone number: (+34) 633112626

Email address: javiersanchezf@hotmail.com

in LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/javiersanchezf

Website: https://github.com/Javisanchezf

• Home: Málaga (Spain)

ABOUT ME

I am a proactive, creative and decisive person, capable of facing challenges and finding effective solutions. I have a great capacity to develop projects with initiative, ambition and camaraderie, becoming evident in experiences such as the development and implementation of a new department in my career.

WORK EXPERIENCE

IT consultant

Lienza Industria Textil S.L.U. [07/2021 - Current]

City: Málaga Country: Spain

- Design and implementation of the Marketing department.
- Responsible for the implementation of SEO, SEM, digital data analysis and digital marketing for customer acquisition, achieving a growth in terms of turnover of 40% per year.
- Creation of corporate website and e-commerce.
- Design and creation of new products through 3D printing.

ERP Consultant | European Department

Avanade (Microsoft Corporation & Accenture LLP) [05/2022 - 09/2022]

Internship program using D365 technology.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Degree in Industrial Management Engineering

Faculty of Engineering, University of Malaga [08/2017 - 10/2022]

Address: Edificio de Ingenierías UMA, Arquitecto Francisco Peñalosa, 6, 29071 Málaga (Spain)

Website: https://www.uma.es/escuela-de-ingenierias-industriales/

Final grade: 7,05

- 1. Scholarship for Academic Excellence in progress 2020.
- 2. Mention in Innovation Systems and Technological Competitiveness.

Cursus - Software Development

42 Foundation | Telefónica Foundation [09/2022 – Current]

Address: Av de Sor Teresa Prat, 15, 29003 Málaga (Spain)

Website: https://www.42malaga.com/

CS50's Introduction to Artificial Intelligence with Python

HarvardX [04/2023 – Current]

University of Malaga Courses 112.5H

Malaga University [02/2022 – 03/2022]

Address: Edificio de Ingenierías UMA, Arquitecto Francisco Peñalosa, 6, 29071 Málaga (Spain)

- Professional project course 50H.
- Digital Competencies Course 37.5H.
- ∘ Soft Skills Course 25H.

Management, Leadership and Team Motivation Course 60H

Euroinnova [12/2019 – 02/2020]

Address: Camino de la Torrecilla 30 Edificio Innova, Oficina 28, 18200 Málaga (Spain)

Final grade: 10

Master in Business Administration and Management 175H

MASSTERCURSOS [12/2017 - 03/2018]

Final grade: 10

Digital Marketing Course 40H

Google | The Open University | IAB Spain [10/2018 - 11/2018]

Final grade: 97,14%

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): Spanish

Other language(s):

English - Certificate B2.2

LISTENING C1 READING C1 WRITING B2

SPOKEN PRODUCTION B2 SPOKEN INTERACTION B2

DIGITAL SKILLS

WEB | SEO | SEM Programs

Wordpress: Advanced / Prestashop: Intermediate / SEO tools: Advanced / SEM tools: Intermediate

Project Management Programs

Trello: Basic / Arena Simulation: Basic / ProjectLibre: Intermediate / Google Drive / Microsoft Office: Advanced

CAD design and 3D printing programs

Rhinoceros 3D: Intermediate / AutoCAD: Basic / Utimater CURA: Intermediate

Software Development

HTML/CSS: Intermediate / C/C++: Advanced / Python: Basic / Git: Intermediate / VM: Intermediate / Shell script: Intermediate